[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Because the question still remains who started the altercation?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "It's absolutely the key.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Isn't that the key question?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "It was -- this record is from the next morning.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "When do we think he treated him?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "We do think that's likely.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Is that likely, do we think?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "There's no way.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Is it likely they're going to chuck a hail Mary pass?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, I would always appear confident whether or not I was confident.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Gloria, if you are prosecuting this, given everything you've seen to date, would you be pretty confident of a conviction now?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Kind of a no lose situation for the defense to be able to call Cate Edwards.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Yes, Dan?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "I mean, Gloria, the stakes are very high here.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Because it is a kind of complicated question as to, will they be able to demonstrate what was in Edwards' head when most of the facts are not in dispute?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Couldn't be higher stakes unless of course the death penalty were involved which of course it's not involved in this case.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "This couldn't be a higher stakes for John Edwards, could it?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Bottom line, this is a really unusual use of the law.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Dan?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Because once you start saying that private donations can be considered campaign contributions, even if they didn't go through the John Edwards for President fund, where does the line get drawn?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "I think absolutely.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Do they get swayed heavily by a man's demeanor?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "I don't want to, no.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Can you imagine that?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "It's my style, yes.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Ring familiar?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "It is a compliment, yes.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Is that a compliment?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Well, this is the first time I've taken it personally.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "What do you think of what's going on with this whole issue right now?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I was in the car and Laura, my wife, texted me.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Where were you when you knew he'd done it?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Yes, it was very emotional.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Emotional?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Well, I don't -- I personally don't look to the bible as an authority document.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "But what do you say to the people who aren't bigots but who have simply been brought up to believe in a religious matter this is fundamentally not what the bible says is right?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "YNCH: Well, there's a lot of smart people who are bigoted.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "How much of bigotry -- how much of bigotry is basically ignorance, do you think?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Yes, like I was sick.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Like you were sick?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Thirties.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "-- you were in your early 20s?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "I was in my 32 when I sent my parents a letter.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Your 30s?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I waited a long time, yes.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "So you've waited a long time?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Did they know?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I have both, yes.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "You now have both?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Haven't you seen \"Man Med\"?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "So you laugh at the role?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "But it's just a great movie, isn't it?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Late, yes.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "How -- do you think, looking back, how lucky were you that fame came to you quite late?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "If I had gotten famous at 21 or 31, even -- I guess I was starting to get famous at 41 -- I would have been blown by this winds of public opinion.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Well, what do you think?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Every once in awhile -- every once in a while I'll look at it.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Do you not read any of that stuff?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Twenty years.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "You have been sober how long now?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Do you ever miss it?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "-- partying, drinking?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Is it a constant battle?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "You know, I'm still pretty anonymous.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Does all this make up for the loss of anonymity?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "It's just such a shame we have this super PAC thing, I could almost cry.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "What is your view of the way the battle has been fought so far?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Does he have to?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I think the overwhelming part of it all has kind of lessened, but yes it does just feel like my God, when it is going to ever stop.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "CNN, prime time talking about your life, given where you've come from?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "I would like to say I didn't have God in my life.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Well, I had taken on another relationship with someone else.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "When did it start going wrong for you?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "More or less, yeah.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "That created just a sort of -- an unbearable pressure, if you like?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "In 1988, as a congratulatory offer, some friends of mine congratulated me for having my first son.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "What was the first time for you?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "It's one of the low points, but I guess the one that sticks out the most was when I was getting ready to feed my kids after three weeks of them not having a balanced home cooked meal.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "ORGAN: When you look back on that, was that the lowest points, do you think?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "Oh yes, sure.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "The people that you met on the streets, did you meet other people with similar stories to you?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "None whatsoever, none whatsoever.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Does it know any class, homelessness?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Nine, seven girls and two boys.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Many would argue -- you had how many children through this?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "At times, yes, sir.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "None whatsoever.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Did you have any idea when you did that little video for that guy how your life may possibly change?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "Well, actually on January 4th of last year, I got a call.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "When did you first realize it was beginning to take off?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "I'm still -- the obsessions and all -- the obsessions and the desires, they come and go.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "What are the challenges still for you, do you think?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "Keeping the faith that there is still a chance for a second chance, or maintaining hope and a desire to do better at some point.", "docId": "120515pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "To those who haven't had that stroke of luck, what is your message to them?", "qSentId": 734}]